jokebuddha.com 2017-12-13

# Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement Coverage**

This is the official Privacy Statement of www.jokebuddha.com Website (Joke Buddha). This Privacy Statement covers how Joke Buddha treats personally identifiable information that Joke Buddha collects and receives. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of other companies that Joke Buddha does not own or control.

 **Personal Information Collection and Use**

You can read, browse and search for jokes on Joke Buddha without having a Joke Buddha account.  
We may keep records about your usage of Joke Buddha, including but not limited to, information on our server logs from your browser, your IP address, information you display or click on in Joke Buddha, contacts you communicate with, opened correspondence and newsletters released and distributed by Joke Buddha via e-mail and transactions with Joke Buddha and our business partners. Additionally, Joke Buddha may set and access cookies on your computer and allows other companies and entities that show advertisements on our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer; however other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not Joke Buddha's Privacy Statement and other companies or entities do not have access to Joke Buddha's cookies.  
Joke Buddha can use your personal information to customize the advertising and content you see on Joke Buddha, improve quality of our design and services, create new features, monitor aggregate metrics, analyze preferences and trends for promotions, better features and Website's functionality, monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns, contact you, conduct research and display targeted advertisements based on your personal information.  
Joke Buddha does not sell, rent or share your personally identifiable information with others except to provide services you have requested. Joke Buddha does not use your personal information for commercial or marketing communication, except in cases where you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.  
Nevertheless, Joke Buddha may use your e-mail address at any time for non-marketing or administrative purposes, including but not limited to, new features or changes on Joke Buddha.  
Joke Buddha can disclose and use your personally identifiable information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Additionally, we will disclose, use and share your personal information in order to examine, investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illicit or illegitimate activities, suspected fraud or scam, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, breach or infringement of Joke Buddha's Terms and Conditions, or as otherwise required by laws of the United States or other country's, state's or territory's applicable jurisdiction. We have the right to transfer your personal information in the event of Joke Buddha being acquired by or merged with another entity.  
Personal information that you willingly and voluntarily disclose online, such as comments added or jokes submitted, becomes publicly available and can be viewed and used by others as permitted through functionality of the Website and under Joke Buddha's Terms and Conditions.

 **Changes to Privacy Statement**

Joke Buddha retains sole rights to alter or revise its Privacy Statement from time to time without any notice given to you, and you agree to be bound by such amendments or changes.

 **Feedback and Questions**

If you have any questions, enquiries or feedback in relation to Joke Buddha's Privacy Statement please sent us email: [a@jokebuddha.com](mailto:a@jokebuddha.com?subject=Enquiries)
